Guide to the Stanford University, Libraries, Department of Special Collections and University Archives, Records SC0756
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Exhibits Department Records, 1969-2010; Accession ARCH_2010_056; 32 Linear Feet; (22 boxes)
  - Here and There / Antiquarian Maps: Clean, Final Text (July -- September 1993) (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Maps: Drafts, Lists of Items (1993) (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Maps: Graphics (1993) (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Maps: Publicity (1993) (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Maps: Receipts and Budget (1993) (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - The Six-Millionth: The Robert Creeley Archive (Oct. 1993 -- Jan. 1994) Announcement (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Creeley: Case Layouts (1993) (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Creeley: Case Titles (1993) (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Creeley: Case Title Samples (1993) (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Creeley: Expenses (1993) (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Creeley: Fax (1993) (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Creeley: Exhibit Text -- original and final proof (1993) (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Creeley: Final Text -- copy for files (1993) (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Creeley: Images -- photos and text (1993) (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Creeley: Keepsake -- color mockups and rough ideas (1993) (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Creeley: Keepsake Final Design (1993) (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Creeley: Notes Fall ‘93 (1993) (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Creeley: Photos shot (1993) (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Creeley: Poster (1993) (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Creeley: Proof sheets and photos shot (1993) (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Creeley: Publicity (1993) (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Creeley: Signatures (1993) (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Creeley: Signs (1993) (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Denise Levertov Exhibit: one case in conjunction with Patrick Nagatani Show, Art Gallery, Fall 1993 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Telling Time: The Nuremberg Chronicle 500 Years On (Feb. -- March 1994) -- Chronologies Exhibit (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Chronicle: Budget and Receipts (1994) (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Chronicle: Exhibit Text (1994) (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Chronicle: Paper Order (1994) (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Chronicle: Signs and Graphics (1994) (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - University Junction: Palo Alto and Stanford, 1890-1920 (Apr-June 1994) -- Graphics (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - University Junction: Exhibit Notes (1994) (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - University Junction: Press Release (1994) (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - University Junction: Signs (1994) (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - University Junction: Text (1994) (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Coming to Terms: Passionate Friendship to Gay Liberation on the Farm (July-Sept. 1994) -- Case Layout (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Coming to Terms: Case Titles (1994) (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Coming to Terms: Expenses (1994) (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Coming to Terms: Historical Society -- Koskovich Talk (1994) (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Coming to Terms: Photocopy of Logbook (1994) (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Coming to Terms: Photographic and Line Images (1994) (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Coming to Terms: Postcards (1994) (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Coming to Terms: Publicity (1994) (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Coming to Terms: Sign (1994) (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Coming to Terms: "Stanford Daily" advertising (1994) (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Coming to Terms: "Stanford Magazine" Jun. 1993, ‘Gays at Stanford' (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Coming to Terms: Stonewall Commemorative Exhibit (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Coming to Terms: Text and Citations (1994) (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Coming to Terms: Type Demolition (1994) (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Coming to Terms: Talking Wall Quotes (1994) (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Of Horses and Horsemanship: Highlights of the Barry Whitehead Collection (Oct. 1994 –Jan 1995) Book Text (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Whitehead: Captions and Citations (1994) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Whitehead: Keepsake Art (1994) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Whitehead: Keepsake Printing and Color Seps (1994) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Whitehead: Kudos (1994) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Whitehead: List and Layout (1994) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Whitehead: Poster/Postcard (1994) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Whitehead: Publicity (1994) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Whitehead: Receipts (1994) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Whitehead: Signs and Large Graphics (1994) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Whitehead: Text Poss. (1994) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Sports Hall of Fame Memo (November 1994) (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - pulp/protest/poetry: collecting the recent past (SF California Antiquarian Bookfair) (Feb 24-26, 1995): Antiquarian Bookfair (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Bookfair: Banner (1995) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Bookfair: Budget and Receipts (1995) (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Bookfair: Captions Complete Final Set/annotated w/ call #s (1995) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Bookfair: Content and Layout (1995) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Bookfair: Floorplan (1995) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Bookfair: SF Concourse Exhibit Space (1995) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Bookfair: Floorplan and Case Maps (1995) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Bookfair: Lists/Text (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Bookfair: Photocopies made for insurance purposes (1995) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Bookfair: Postcard (1995) (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Bookfair: 1995 program (1995) (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Bookfair: Publicity photo shoot (1995) (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Bookfair: Text -- welcome and introduction (1995) (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Bookfair: Type and Lettering (1995) (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Windows to the Mind: Selected Books from Stanford Special Collections (mounted by the Palo Alto Cultural Center) (Feb 23-Apr. 30 1995) (GUNST) (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Windows: Winter ‘95 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Favorite Books of ASUL: Loan Forms (Feb -- Apr 1995) (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Favorite Books: Signs/Captions/Case Maps/Correspondence (1995) (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - The Bread of Days/el pan de los dias: The Yolla Bolly Press (March 1995) (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Eadweard Muybridge: The Archaeology of Film (April 1995) -- in conjunction with Stanford Theatre (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Muybridge: Linda Long's Notes (1995) (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - The Athlete's Body: 1-case Show / Hall of Fame (May 1995) (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Going to the Source: Stanford Students Encounter the Far West (May-July 1995) (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Far West: Captions and Citations (1995) (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Far West: Case Titles and Sign (1995) (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Far West: Graphics (1995) (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Far West: Postcard (1995) (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Anglo Saxon Studies at Stanford (August-September 1995) (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Cannery Row: John Steinbeck at Stanford (Sept.-Dec. 1995) (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Cannery Row: Captions/Case Titles/Citations (1995) (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Cannery Row: Graphics (1995) (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Cannery Row: Receipts and Expenses (1995) (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Cannery Row: Steinbeck at Stanford (1995) (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - The Critic as Collector: a Literary Critic's Working Collection of Beerbohm, Neruda and Celan (Felstiner Event) October 1995 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Stanford v. California: Big Game Programs from the Nineties to the Fifties (Nov. 1995) (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - New in the Book Arts (11/95-1/96) (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - How to Book a Read: On Legibility (Jan. -- Mar. 1996) Text and Citations (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - How to: Text and Layouts (1996) (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Of Vases and Volcanoes (April 1996) (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Freedom, Anxiety, Engagement: Ten Years of Jewish Studies at Stanford (April-May 1996) Case 1 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Jewish Studies: Case 2 -- Origins of the Jewish Studies Program (1996) (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Jewish Studies: Case 3 -- Jewish Life at Stanford (1996) (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Jewish Studies: Case 4 -- Jewish Life (1996) (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Jewish Studies: Case 5 -- Salo Baron (1996) (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Jewish Studies: Case 6 -- Salo Baron, continued. (1996) (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Jewish Studies: Fishman Request for Photo of Poem (1996) (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Jewish Studies: Item Lists (1996) (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Jewish Studies: Labels (1996) (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Jewish Studies: Marvin Friedman drawing permission (1996) (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Jewish Studies: Postcard (1996) (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Catching the Light: Stegner mini-exhibit -- sign (May -- October 1996) (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Talent, Voice, Vision: Creative Writing at Stanford (May-Oct. 1996) -- Case Back Graphics (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Creative Writing: Case Title and Caption Examples (1996) (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Creative Writing: First Drafts/Last Drafts (1996) (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Creative Writing: Notes (1996) (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Creative Writing: Exhibit Sign (1996) (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Creative Writing: Text and Citations for File (1996) (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Mallormèana (Oct. 21-27, 1996) (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Wyslawa Szymborska Nobel Exhibit (November 1996) (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Stanford the Farm (Nov. 1996 -- Feb. 1997) (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - The Look of Reason (January 1997) (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Mark Twain (February 1997) (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Braude Exhibit (May 1997) (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Before the Dismal Science: The Gustave Gimon Collection of French Political Economy (February -- April 1997) -- Bookplate and Croix de Lorraine Info (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Gimon: Case Maps (1997) (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Gimon: Catalogue Annotated Copy (1997) (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Gimon: Catalogue early trials design and trials and notes (1997) (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Gimon: Catalogue edited drafts (1997) (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Gimon: Catalogue estimates and final printing specs/instr. (1997) (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Gimon: Catalogue file copy (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Gimon: Catalogue laser proof sent to Chase Printing w/ files on disk (1997) (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Gimon: Catalogue J Beecher loan of photos and negatives (1997) (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Gimon: Front Matter Drafts (1997) (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Gimon: Graphics/Layout (1997) (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Gimon: Line Art/Scanned (1997) (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Gimon: Notes/Schedule (1997) (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Gimon: Event info/Announcement/dinner invitation (1997) (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Gimon: Panel -- Beecher Talk (1997) (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Gimon: Panel -- Lougee-Chappell (1997) (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Gimon: panel -- publicity (1997) (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Gimon: Catalogue Paper (1997) (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Gimon: Receipts (1997) (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Gimon: Sign (1997) (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Notes from the Underground: The Building of the London Sewers (March-June 1997) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Underground: Booklet (1997) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - African Postcards Exhibit: Curated by Grad Student Brian Hollis (April 1997) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - The Times of His Lives: William Saroyan (May-July 1997) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Saroyan: Annotated Item Lists and Case Maps (1997) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Saroyan: Armenian School 8th Graders Visit to Saroyan Exhibition (3/29/97) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Saroyan: Event/Announcement, Early Planning (1997) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Saroyan: Keepsake Concept, Original Texts, Production Schedule (1997) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Saroyan: Keepsake Design Trials (1997) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Saroyan: Keepsake email correspondence (1997) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Saroyan: Keepsake estimates, copy of printing bill (1997) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Saroyan: Keepsake file copy (1997) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Saroyan: How Magazine Design Competition -- decided not to enter (1997) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Saroyan: Letters for Keepsake (1997) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Saroyan: Keepsake old draft (1997) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Saroyan: Keepsake photo (1997) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Saroyan: Keepsake storage location (1997) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Saroyan: Keepsake Laser proofs of edited TIFF files (1997) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Saroyan: Publicity and Event (1997) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Saroyan: Receipts and Expenses (see also 3NAP060 expenses folder) (1997) (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Saroyan: Sign (1997) (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Saroyan: signature used in exhibit sign and cartoon (1997) (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Saroyan: Typeface research (1997) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Bloomsbury Art in Bay Area Collections (Spring 1997) (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Gary Snyder Conference and Exhibit (1997 -- Not Produced) (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Polish Artists' Books Exhibit (August -- November 1997) (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Polish: Catalog of 1997 Warsaw Exhibit File Copy (1997) (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Polish: Sign (1997) (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Polish: Texts and Press Release (1997) (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - 100th Big Game (November 1997) (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Votes for Women -- Unfinished Business (December 1997-January 1998) BINDER (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Suffrage: Correspondence and notes (1997) (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Suffrage: drafts of text (1997) (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Suffrage: Huntington orientation (1997) (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Suffrage: Items displayed from SUL Collection (1997) (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Suffrage: Mailing to ASUL (1997) (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Suffrage: Nancy Pinckert visit (1997) (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Suffrage: Events poster (1997) (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Suffrage: Poster Distribution to Local Public Libraries and Bookstores (1997) (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Suffrage: Press Release and Publicity (1997) (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Suffrage: Printed Mats (1997) (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Suffrage: "Report to the Huntington" follow-up and copies of enclosures sent (1997) (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Suffrage: SU Companion Exhibit (1997) (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - New in Special Collections (February -- March 1998) (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - New: Exhibit Invitation (1998) (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - New: Case maps (1998) (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Apple Memo photocopies (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Sunset Magazine centennial exhibit (Spring/Summer 1998) (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Miscellany Britannica / Alethya Avilan -- Victorian Children (April-June 1998) (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Britannica: Booklet (1998) (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Britannica: Daniel Davis, David Solomons -- Forgotten Champion of Anglo-Saxon Emancipation (1998) (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Britannica: Elizabeth Logan / Beatrix Potter (1998) (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Britannica: File copy text and captions (1998) (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Britannica: TW Stanford (1998) (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Britannica: Melissa Gleason -- Fires Were Started (1998) (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Britannica: Robin Moroney -- True Blue Ideals of the Empire (1998) (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Britannica: Sign and Invitation (1998) (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Britannica: notes (1998) (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Britannica: Time Log (1998) (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Britannica: Will Shearin / The Lee Papers (1998) (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Medieval Manuscripts conference (March 26-28) (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - The Mouse that Roared (December 1998) (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Mouse: Event 12/7/98 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Mouse: Event Correspondence (1998) (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Humanities Series Stuff: 1998 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Humanities Series: Presidential Lectures Series (Winter-Spring 1999) (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Hum. Series: Winter 1999 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Building and Rebuilding 1989-1999 (1999) (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Reopening: Art and Architecture/Ross (1999) (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Reopening: British and American Literature (1999) (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Reopening: Caption and Casehead trials (1999) (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Reopening: Case Maps 1-20 (1999) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Reopening: Case Maps (1999) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Reopening: Catalog (1999) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Reopening: Citations/Captions master set (1999) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Reopening: Classics/Mustain (1999) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Reopening: Events and Publications (1999) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Reopening: Floorplan (1999) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Reopening: French and Italian/Parrine (1999) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Reopening: Germanic/Lowood (1999) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Reopening: Gunst (1999) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Reopening: History of Science/Lowood (1999) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Reopening: Item prepsheets (1999) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Reopening: Judaica and Hebraica (1999) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Reopening: Latin/Mexican-American (1999) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Reopening: Linguistics and Anthropology (1999) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Reopening: Linotext color samples (1999) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Reopening: Maps (1999) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Reopening: Marine Biology (1999) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Reopening: Music (1999) (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Reopening: Nominations/Notes (1999) (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Reopening: Old Copies of Reopening List (1999) (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Reopening: Page-Turning schedule (1999) (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Reopening: Postcard (1999) (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Reopening: Press Release (1999) (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Reopening: Item Prepsheets cases 1-12 (1999) (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Reopening: Production Checklist (1999) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Reopening: Receipts and Expenses (1999) (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Reopening: RGT to Curators (1999) (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Reopening: Signs (1999) (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Reopening: Slavic (1999) (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Reopening: Social Science (1999) (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Reopening: Texts (1999) (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Reopening: Tiled Printout of Reopening Exhibit Sign (1999) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Reopening: To-Do Lists (1999) (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Reopening: University Archives (1999) (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Reopening: U.S. and British History (1999) (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Reopening: The West Wing (1999) (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Reopening: Green West (1999) (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Reopening: West Wing Rotunda Photos (1999) (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Reopening: Ed Clay Notes on Rotunda Oak Table (1999) (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Reopening: Brayton and Hughes Drawings (1999) (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Reopening: Brayton and Hughes Drawings Table (1999) (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Reopening: Work Schedule (1999) (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Treasures of the Israel Cohen Collection (conference March 22, 2000) (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Israel Cohen: Publication (2000) (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - The Heart Unguarded: The William Abrahams Papers (April 2000) (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Abrahams: Correspondence (2000) (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Abrahams: Design (2000) (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Abrahams: Focus Magazine Article (2000) (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Abrahams: Inventory and Distribution (2000) (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Abrahams: File copies of label types (2000) (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Abrahams: Labels (2000) (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Abrahams: Notes (2000) (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Abrahams: Original Manuscript (2000) (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Abrahams: Page Proofs from Plates (2000) (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Abrahams: Permissions (2000) (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Abrahams: Philippe's Intro (2000) (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Abrahams: Printers Dummy and Color Samples (2000) (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Abrahams: Printing poetry ch. 5 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Abrahams: Polymer Plates [heavy] (2000) (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Abrahams: Proof (2000) (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Abrahams: Marked proofs (2000) (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Abrahams: Specs and Estimates, copy of invoice (2000) (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Abrahams: Specs for estimate (Yolla Bolly) (2000) (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Abrahams: various dummies (2000) (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Abrahams: extra covers (2000) (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Conceptual Art and the Document (April, 1999) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - John Steinbeck: From Salinas to Stockholm (January-April 2000) -- "Splash" intro case map (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Steinbeck: Case 1 -- Salinas Valley Childhood (2000) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Steinbeck: Case 2 -- The Stanford Years, 1919-1925 (2000) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Steinbeck: Case 3 -- Apprenticeship (2000) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Steinbeck: Case 4 -- First Novel, 1929 Cup of Gold (2000) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Steinbeck: Case 5 -- Return to the Long Valley (2000) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Steinbeck: Case 6 -- Popular Success (2000) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Steinbeck: Case 7 -- CA Depression Politics (2000) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Steinbeck: Case 8 -- The Grapes of Wrath (2000) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Steinbeck: Case 9 -- Retreat From Politics (2000) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Steinbeck: Case 10 -- Writer as Patriot (2000) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Steinbeck: Case 11 -- Mexico (2000) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Steinbeck: Case 12 -- Hollywood, 1940s (2000) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Steinbeck: Case 13 -- Re-imagining CA (2000) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Steinbeck: Case 14 -- Europe (2000) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Steinbeck: Case 15 -- Searching for America (2000) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Steinbeck: Case 16 -- Stockholm/Nobel Celebrity (2000) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Steinbeck: Cases 19 and 20 -- The Yolla Bolly Press Editions (2000) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Steinbeck: Translations Case (2000) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Steinbeck: Catalog -- Cover Design (2000) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Steinbeck: Catalog -- Distribution and Sales (2000) (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Steinbeck: Catalog -- Expenses (2000) (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Steinbeck: Catalog -- File copy (2000) (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Steinbeck: Catalog -- Images for Reproduction/Permissions (2000) (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Steinbeck: Catalog -- Notes (2000) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Steinbeck: Catalog -- Permission Requests (2000) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Steinbeck: Catalog -- Preliminary Design (2000) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Steinbeck: Catalog -- Proofs (2000) (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Steinbeck: Catalog -- Scanned Images (2000) (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Steinbeck: Catalog -- Sent to Publishers Press, 2/16/00 (2000) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Steinbeck: Catalog -- Specs/Estimates (2000) (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Steinbeck: Correspondence (2000) (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Steinbeck: Expenses (2000) (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Steinbeck: Guestbook (2000) (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Steinbeck: Invitation and Postcard (2000) (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Steinbeck: Lettering for Catalog and Exhibit Sign (2000) (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Steinbeck: Letters and Copies (2000) (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Steinbeck: Notes (2000) (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Steinbeck: Timeline and Production Schedule (2000) (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Steinbeck: Publicity (2000) (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Steinbeck: Publicity (2000) (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Becky's Layouts and Texts (2000) (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- CA Depression/Grapes of Wrath (2000) (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Case Notes (2000) (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Case Text Drafts (2000) (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Case Texts (2000) (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Catalog Drafts (2000) (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Elaine Steinbeck Obits (2000) (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Event Notes (2000) (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- International Reputation (2000) (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- James Cummins Correspondence (2000) (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Layouts (2000) (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Mexico (2000) (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Miscellaneous (2000) (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Nobel Fame (2000) (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Patriot (2000) (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Popular Success: Tortilla Flat and Of Mice and Men (2000) (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Reimaging CA (2000) (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Retreat from Controversy (2000) (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Return to the Lone Valley (2000) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Salinas Childhood (2000) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Searching for America (2000) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Splash Case/Intro Case (2000) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Steinbeck Collection (2000) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Steinbeck in Europe (2000) (Box 8, Folder 6)